math-drills.com 2017-04-07

# Math-Drills.Com Privacy and Cookies Policy

This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information received and collected by Math-Drills.com and how it is used.

What? Math Drills.com and its partners set cookies on your computer or device as you access the website. This is done by almost all websites and should not be a surprise nor should it cause you too much concern. Math-Drills.com has far fewer privacy implications than most websites. We don't think it is appropriate for everyone and their dog to know about your browsing habits, so we have taken steps to minimize the ability of third parties to track you, and there are steps you can take to further minimize how you are tracked.

Why do we need to track our visitors at all? Math-Drills.com tracks our visitors for two specific purposes: 1. to gain insight into how the website is used and 2. to comply with requirements of our advertising partners. Our third party partners track our visitors for their own purposes which you can read about further down this page.

## What does Math-Drills.com do?

Math-Drills.com keeps track of its visitors using server access logs. The information inside the server access logs includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks. We use this information to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. We do not share this information with any third parties other than in the most general sense. For example, we might tell someone how many visitors we had on a certain day.

Math-Drills.com may set cookies on your computer for various reasons, none of which are nefarious. To find any cookies set by Math-Drills.com, you should look for cookies from "math-drills.com" using the view cookies functionality in your browser.

Math-Drills.com collects email addresses and names through a double-opt-in process. You do not need to supply your email address to access our website, only if you wish to receive email news and updates from us. An unsubscribe link is available in every email that we send.

Math-Drills.com provides links to external websites. There are links to various external websites from Math-Drills.com pages including social media websites, Amazon websites, advertising partner websites, advertisers, and websites provided to users for more information. These external websites have their own privacy and cookie policies. We recognize that there are serious privacy concerns with certain websites, such as Facebook, but we provide links to them anyway as large numbers of visitors already use such sites and have agreed to their terms.

## What does Math-Drills.com do to protect your privacy?

No Social Media. Although you will see social media buttons on the website, these are simple links and have no third party involvement unless you click/tap on one of those links.

No Third Party Analytics Code. Most websites include third party code, such as Google Analytics, to track your use of a website. We have decided not to use such tracking code since it serves very little purpose to us, slows down your navigation of the website, and has privacy implications.

No Bloat. We try very hard to have an extremely fast loading website without the bloat of many other websites. This means we don't force you to load any unnecessary scripts. This also means that we have fewer privacy impacts since we rely on our own website code.

## What do third parties on Math-Drills.com do?

Math-Drills uses Google Adsense, Media.net and Amazon to serve ads to visitors. These services may set a wide variety of cookies on your computer. If you are not interested in having those cookies set on your computer, you can disable third party cookies in your browser. You will most likely still see advertisements on the website, but tracking cookies from those advertisements will not be set. Adsense and Media.net may set a math-drills.com cookie even if you have third party cookies disabled in your browser. This cookie may look like it came from math-drills.com, but it was set by a third party.

Third party vendors, including Google, Media.net and Amazon, use cookies to serve ads based on your prior visits to Math-Drills.com. Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to you based on your visit to Math-Drills.com and/or other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Google Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/)

Consult the respective privacy policies of our third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Math-Drills.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

Read more about [Google's Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/) and [Google's Advertising Privacy](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/)

Read more about [Media.net's Ad Preferences](http://www.media.net/adchoices) and [Media.net's Privacy Policy](http://www.media.net/privacy-policy)

Read more about [Amazon Advertising Preferences](https://www.amazon.com/adprefs) and [Amazon's Privacy Notice](https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html?nodeId=468496)

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us using our Feedback Page

The best way to protect your privacy on the internet is NOT to use the internet!

### Arithmetic

### Other Math Topics

### Holiday Math Worksheets

### Interactive Math
